
export const quizQuestions_2 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does JSX stand for in React?',
      choices: ['JavaScript XML', 'JSX Syntax', 'JavaScript Extensions', 'JS XML'],
      correctAnswer: 'JavaScript XML',
    },
    {
      question: 'In JSX, how can you embed JavaScript expressions?',
      choices: ['Using {{ curly braces }}', 'With %percentage% signs', 'Using double curly braces {{}}', 'By using single curly braces {}'],
      correctAnswer: 'By using single curly braces {}',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is a valid JSX element?',
      choices: ['<div class="container">Content</div>', '<div className="container">Content</div>', '<div>Content</div>', '<span>Text</span>'],
      correctAnswer: '<div className="container">Content</div>',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do you comment in JSX?',
      choices: ['// Comment', '<!-- Comment -->', '{/* Comment */}', '/* Comment */'],
      correctAnswer: '{/* Comment */}',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the "className" attribute in JSX?',
      choices: ['To define a class in CSS', 'To apply styles in-line', 'To specify a class for a React component', 'To add a class to a JavaScript object'],
      correctAnswer: 'To specify a class for a React component',
    },
    {
      question: 'In JSX, how do you render a list of items?',
      choices: ['Using the map() method', 'With a for loop', 'Using the renderList() function', 'By concatenating strings'],
      correctAnswer: 'Using the map() method',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the "style" attribute in JSX?',
      choices: ['To define internal styles', 'To include external stylesheets', 'To apply inline styles', 'To link external CSS files'],
      correctAnswer: 'To apply inline styles',
    },
    {
      question: 'In JSX, how do you render a component conditionally?',
      choices: ['Using if-else statements', 'With switch statements', 'By using the ternary operator', 'Conditional rendering is not possible in JSX'],
      correctAnswer: 'By using the ternary operator',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can you include dynamic content in JSX?',
      choices: ['By using the eval() function', 'Using string interpolation', 'By concatenating strings', 'Through props and state'],
      correctAnswer: 'Through props and state',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the "dangerouslySetInnerHTML" attribute in React?',
      choices: ['To include HTML content from a trusted source', 'To add inline styles', 'To create dynamic class names', 'To prevent XSS attacks'],
      correctAnswer: 'To include HTML content from a trusted source',
    },
  ],
}